na na na na
I have it.
hmm
ah?
Hello?
Uh, this is Yui Ishizaki.
Huh?
Please wait a minute.
Yes, ma'am.
Ah!
Mr. Nagayama?
Yes, it's Mr. Nagayama.
It's Mr. Nagayama. I knew it! It's his voice!
How do you know? It's been a long time. Long time no see.
It's Mr. Nagayama!
I'm afraid you'll get angry if I call you "Hiyuhida" or "Hiyuhida"...
But you're still Hiyuu.
It's been a while.
How long has it been?
It's the first time we've talked on the phone.
Yeah, I guess so.
Probably.
I've been thinking about it, and I don't think it's the first time.
Are you sure?
Yeah.
We said we'd have a drink at least once.
Was it a phone call?
Or was it an e-mail?
We e-mailed back and forth a few times.
Yes, of course.
Yes, Mr. Nagayama!
I miss it.
It's been a long time.
It's been 20 years.
Yes, it's been 20 years.
How old are you now?
I'm 37 now.
Then it's been more than 20 years.
It's been more like 20 years.
I haven't seen you in 14 years.
I was in eighth grade, right?
It's great to see you again.
You're doing great.
I've been wanting to ask you about that time.
Anything you want. What do you want to ask?
I don't know.
Do you remember?
No, I... I... I...
I'm a little hazy on some things.
Yeah, yeah.
I don't know.
I'm...
It's just because I'm...
That's why, um, Rama's play...
Your play...
It's probably the first time for me to express myself.
It's my first time.
In front of an audience.
You have to pay for the ticket.
Yes, sir.
I think it was the first time for me to say, "Yes.
I think it was the first time for me to do that in front of an audience.
I started music when I was in the third grade of junior high school.
I started music... and this is how I am now...
Yes.
I always think about Mr. Nagayama at that time...
You know...
When I was in the eighth grade...
After it was over
I think he asked me if I wanted to do the play with him again.
I did.
You did, didn't you?
And then...
I said...
I'm not sure if you answered or not.
At that time, Shirai-kun was nodding his head.
But he said he wanted to do it.
But I heard you started music right away.
I see.
That's right.
It doesn't have to be music or acting.
I thought you often wanted to express yourself.
I thought I could always do a play.
I still think so. No, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, it's true. I mean, that's my line, but...
But really, that's still the case, so it's an ongoing project for me.
I'm glad to hear that.
I'm glad. That's what I'd like you to do, even if it's not with me.
I'm glad.
Because I got to play the lead.
You did, didn't you? Yes, I did.
It was the first original script I ever wrote, and the first lead role I ever played. So that was your very first script?
I had directed a book he had written, but this was the first time I wrote a script for everyone by myself.
I still think it's amazing.I still think it's great.
Oh!
Oh my God!
Remember when the wind blows between the stars? That's crazy.
Wow!
I've been trying to figure out what the original title was, but I haven't come up with it yet.
Yes, yes, yes.
I was just wondering if Hewickon remembers.
I remember... it's a letter in the wind.
Huh! That's it!
That's it.
That's great!
I remember that.
The wind letter, the wind letter, that's it.
That's so good!
What? Say the line again.
The wind blows between the stars
That star... Oh, no, between that star and that star.
Oh, no, no, between the stars.
The wind blows between the stars.
What was it, something in between that...
There's something between the star and the star...
Between the star and the star...
I don't know...
Yeah, it's like they're echoing each other or something.
It's holding them together.
Oh, yeah, something like that
That's what it was.
Yeah, something like that
I don't know...
I'm reminded of it a lot.
Really?
Do you remember what role Huey played when he said that line?
Yes, I remember.
It was a role called "Kakeru".
You even remember the character's name.
Yes, I remember.
That's amazing.
I'm going to play it.
President of the student council.
Yes, I was the student council president.
Yeah, a little hard.
That's why my friends and I grew apart.
That's right.
You go to the library, read a book, read a book...
And then Gauche comes out, and you soften up
And then you become soft and gentle.
And when you soften...
I don't know how to say it... the ghosts that were helping me... the ghosts... or the people around them...
But in the end they disappear, and he says, "It's going to be okay now." It's very sad.
I wrote a good story. It's a really good story.
But you know... that was a bit of a shock to me.
I couldn't have written it otherwise.
He was desperate. I was desperate too.
Did I inspire you a little? Of course, of course. When we were in the rehearsal room, and I saw the way you said it, and the way you said it with the others...
I saw how you said things and how you talked to other people, and how you were rather calm, right?
I think that kind of human touch probably played a role.
I was probably just trying to look cool.
I've made a lot of films over the years.
I started making them when I was about 20 years old.
Around 20?
I've been doing music for a long time.
I didn't write lyrics myself.
I started writing songs when I was about 20.
I started writing songs about the stars, didn't I?
Yes, there was a public song about the planets, wasn't there?
That's right.
That's how you made your debut.
Is there anything that's stayed with you? Did it influence you at that time?
I think it has. The very beginning of my expression was related to the stars, so...
I don't know what it is, but I think I will continue to express myself with that in mind.
I'm not sure what it is, but I think I'm going to express myself with that in mind.
Huey's words after he started writing his own words are very interesting to me.
Oh, really?
Are you listening to me? Mr. Nagayama.
He's listening.
Maybe not in a super-enthusiastic way.
But it still bugs me... one by one.
The title says "Kabin".
It's still bothering me.
So...
I've heard about it a lot, and not just because I was involved.
Yes, yes, yes...
There are a lot of adults who say it's fine.
Really?
Yes.
It was the first time in my life that I concentrated on something.
I think it was the first time in my life that I concentrated on something for the first time in my life.
I think it was the first time in my life that I was able to concentrate on something for the first time in my life.
And the timing between the character of Huey and the character of the role.
When he said, "I wish we could talk at the same time.
I don't know if it's true or not.
Anyway
I was surprised, wasn't I? Remember that?
When we were rehearsing for the stage when the other artists arrived.
I wondered why they talked so normally and let the truth take over.
Me?
Yes. It sounds like you're speaking for the first time.
I could understand the flow of the play very well, even though it sounded like I was speaking for the first time.He understands the flow of the play very well.
I mean, I understand it, or rather, I'm making it. I was making it.
I was very proud of that.
Right? I was very proud of that. I was really proud of that.
Was I really that good?
But I think it was really your ability to concentrate.
So, first of all, the power of concentration, and then the way the words came out of his mouth,
I was surprised at how pure the words came out of his mouth.
I was surprised at that, so I thought that even if I wrote a slightly racy or beautiful line like that, I would still be able to speak without lying.
So, I thought that even if I wrote a slightly racy or beautiful line like that, I would be able to speak without lying.
It was a word that could have come out sounding a bit creepy.
It starts with "constellation," "starry night.
I said "starry night.
From the first magnitude to the eighth magnitude.
to 8th magnitude with the naked eye... but there are more stars we can't see.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
I remember that line. It's embarrassing, but it's a good one.
I think I'm still influenced by it.
Even now? Even now.
I don't want to sound like I'm responsible for it.
But, again, Huey made me write it. I'm so glad.
I'm glad to hear that. I'm glad you remember me like that.
I also remember...
The last day?
The last day.
I don't know...
I couldn't do it right.
I cried.
Yes, yes, I cried.
That's right.
Was it because I couldn't do it right?
I don't know.
I don't think so.
I couldn't stop.
He didn't come out of the dressing room.
That's why.
What was that all about?
Well, you know...
Well, you see...
You didn't come out of the dressing room for a long time.
To be honest, you didn't come out for the same amount of time as the play.
You didn't come out for the same amount of time as the play.
The play was about an hour and a half to two hours long.
And you didn't come out for the same amount of time.
Wow.
That's amazing.
And then...
I knocked on the door to see if he was okay, and he came out.
She was crying. She was still crying.
And then he went up on stage.
He said he'd lost her, and she cried again.
Oh, I see. So you're taking the place down?
Yeah, they were clearing out, and the show was over.
Oh, my God.
What's that?
That's so touching.
That's amazing. That's so amazing. I met a girl like that.
I remember it so well.
We talked about how we would see each other again if we did the play again.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Yes... yes... yes... yes... yes... yes...
But for me, he's been expressing himself for a long time, so I see him as if he's doing a play.
Really? Yes, it's true.
Hiuyu, as I told you before.
I had a calligrapher friend of mine write the lyrics to "A Midsummer's Eve" for me.
I have it on my wall.
Huey, do you have any lyrics of your own that you'd like to share with us?
This one?
I don't know.
I don't know. I guess I'm just trying to find a unique way to say it.
I don't mean like that.
I mean, when you come up with words that have no decoration, or no Terai, or something like that...
I like the feel of it better now.
I like the way it feels.
I don't want it to be a riddle to be solved.
I mean, of course, you can write it that way, but it's not like a riddle, it's just...
I think it's very difficult to write something that can reach people's hearts in such a simple way.
I think you're right.
Since we're here, why don't you tell us your favorite phrase on the phone?
What's your favorite phrase?
I wonder.
For example, on the current album or the new album.
Yes, sir.
What did you write about?
Let's see...
Uh...
Okay.
Wait a minute.
Next time, I'll go through my haggis-filled days.
Someday, when I polish these pieces, I want to see you shining like a diamond, splashing around.
It's like, "I was just imagining something like that right now.
I've been imagining that right now.
That's wonderful.
Yes, it is.
I wonder what that is.
The distance between you and what you're imagining is really nice.
Thank you very much.
When you say that it has a bit of a lived-in feel to it...When the word "living" is used, it is too much to say "I did it.
It's not that I'm not trying to live a certain way, but...
I don't think you are trying to live your life in a particular way, but...
Do you try not to stray too far from that lifestyle?
Do you pay attention to your eyes?
I don't know. I don't take notes or anything, and I don't think about anything.
Usually.
Yes, I do. If I think about it, it would be difficult, or if I start thinking like that.
Yes, that's pretty much the case now.
There are times when I have a sudden flash of inspiration, but...
It's like the Olympics.
It is very difficult to hold the Olympics.
I think the words you just used are pretty good.
Okay, then
Next day!
Wow
That's right. That's right.
Like, "Let's go fight.
But that's what it's all about, isn't it? It's about having a normal life.
Yes, I think so.
I think that's where the drawer is.
Yes, there are.
I've prepared it for you.
That's great.
Open it.
Is this possible?
Oh, what? A letter!
What's this?
What's this? A letter?
Oh, it's a letter.
Yes, thank you
I wrote it.
Can I read it?
Can Huey read it?
Can I read it? Yes. Then I'll be glad if Hughie reads it.
I'll be glad if Huey reads it.
Can I read it? Oh, my God, I'm gonna cry.
Come on, Mr. Huey.
After a long day in the dressing room.
I went back to see the play.
When I went there after he was gone...
I'll never forget his face.
I'll never forget her voice.
The honesty in her voice.
Words that never lied.
The passion that you conveyed with your whole body
What has not changed since I was 14 years old
The things that keep changing
I see you walking far and wide with so many things in your arms
I'm always dazzled by you
Yo, Nagayama
Thank you very much.
I'm on my way.
Great. I'm so happy.
Oh, it's gone.
But...
I'm hoping it's just a memory of a time when I did it.
I'm glad you remember it so well.
But that's why it's so appealing.
You think it's attractive, right?
Maybe so.
I'm going to lose it.
And the expression.
Maybe so.
Wow.
I'm just going to leave it like this for a second.
The lyrics.
Thank you very much.
Thank you, Mr. Nakayama.
No problem at all.
Let's do it again.
Yes.
Not necessarily on stage, but just to talk together... for a moment.
What do you want from me?
I'll call you later, Mr. Nagai. I'll call you myself.
Thank you for your letter.
A letter from the wind, or from one person to another?
Thank you very much.
See you later.
Excuse me.